School of Medicine Records UA010
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, teaching materials, and programs, 1893 -- 2019; 1897 -- 1937; UA010.004; 6.2 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 2 Digital Object(s)
  - School of Medicine graduating class photograph, 1940; UA010.004.042.00012.000002; .2 Linear Feet (Box Shared 36)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Donated by Alys Anne Wiedeke, 2019, accession UA-2019-069.
  - Medical School Commencement invitation and program, 1924; UA010.000837 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Medical School Class of 1924 panoramic photograph, UA010.000838 (Box 17)
    Open for research. Fragile condition- please consult with archivist.
  - Medical School Class of 1932 panoramic photograph, UA010.000842 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 4)
    Transferred by Fran Foret, 2019, accession UA-2020-012.
  - School of Medicine White Coat Ceremony programs, 1996 -- 2019; UA010.000839; 0.1 Linear Feet (Box 44, Folder 6)
    White Coat Ceremony programs from 1999, 2000, 2002, 2009, 2011, 2016-2019.
    Transferred by the Tufts University School of Medicine, 2019, accession UA-2020-034.
  - School of Medicine Awards Dinner Dance and Family Day programs, 1982 -- 2012; UA010.000840; 0.1 Linear Feet (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Transferred by the Tufts University School of Medicine, 2019, accession UA-2020-036.
    School of Medicine Senior Dinner Dance and Awards Night programs from 1982-1983, 1985, 1987-1991, 1994-1995, 2000-2005, 2009, and 2012. Award recipients pamphlet included for 1985, 1988-1991, 1994-1995, 2001-2003, 2005, 2009, and 2012. Family Day program, October 1996.
  - School of Medicine event pamphlets, memorial service programs, and information for students, 1993 -- 2010; UA010.000841; 0.1 Linear Feet (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Transferred by the Tufts University School of Medicine, 2019, accession UA-2020-037
    Contains Diversity Day program, 1993; U.S. Army Medical Detachment Boston Health Care Recruiting Team Commissioning Ceremony, 1997; Third Year Orientation pamphlet, 2006; Memorial Service programs for Janet Cooper (1993) and Clark T. Sawin (2004); information about 2009-2010 TUSM Learning Communities; Lawrence Bacow (2002) and John Dibiaggio (1993) inauguration programs; publication with general information about School of Medicine.
- Additional accessions, circa 1934 -- 2017; UA010.005
  - Jaharis Center studies and reports, UA010-001 (Box 1)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Jaharis Center studies and reports, UA010-002 (Box 2)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-003 (Box 3)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-004 (Box 4)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-005 (Box 5)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-006 (Box 6)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-007 (Box 7)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-008 (Box 8)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-009 (Box 9)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-010 (Box 10)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-011 (Box 11)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-012 (Box 12)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-013 (Box 13)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-014 (Box 14)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-015 (Box 15)
  - Jaharis Center plans, UA010-016 (Box 16)
  - Programs and bulletins, UA010-017 (Box 17)
  - Medical School Photos, UA010-018 (Box 19)
  - Slides of Construction Projects and Faculty, 1979 -- 1983; UA010-019 (Box 20)
  - Reports, scrapbook, and letters, 1934 -- 1980; UA010-020 (Box 21)
  - Groundbreaking shovel, Arthur M. Sackler Center for Medical Education, 1983-11-18; UA010-021 (Box 22)
    Groundbreaking shovel from Arthur M. Sackler Center for Medical Education groundbreaking ceremony, November 18, 1983.
  - Professorships at Tufts University School of Medicine catalog, 2017; UA010.005.022; 0.1 Folder(s) (Box 17)
    2 copies of "Professorships at Tufts University School of Medicine" catalog published in 2017, detailing the history of each fund and biographies of the current holders of each professorship.
    Transferred by the Tufts University School of Medicine, 2017, accession UA-2018-008.